<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Hrishikesh Singh</title>
    <link>https://hrishikeshh.github.io/finalweb/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Hrishikesh Singh</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 23:15:00 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hrishikeshh.github.io/finalweb/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Driver Drowsiness Detection system 📢</title>
      <link>https://hrishikeshh.github.io/finalweb/projects/d3s/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 23:15:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hrishikeshh.github.io/finalweb/projects/d3s/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Every year, traffic accidents due to human errors cause increasing amounts of deaths and injuries globally. To help reduce the amount of fatalities, in the paper presented here, a new module for Advanced Driver Assistance System (ADAS) which deals with automatic driver drowsiness detection based on visual information and Artificial Intelligence is presented.
The aim of this system is to locate, track, and analyze both the drivers face and eyes to compute a drowsiness index, where this real-time system works under varying light conditions (diurnal and nocturnal driving).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pacific Dynamics 📢</title>
      <link>https://hrishikeshh.github.io/finalweb/projects/pd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 23:15:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hrishikeshh.github.io/finalweb/projects/pd/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Something
Here&amp;rsquo;s the Code</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post Collegiate Income Prediction 🏛💲 </title>
      <link>https://hrishikeshh.github.io/finalweb/projects/post-college/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 23:15:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hrishikeshh.github.io/finalweb/projects/post-college/</guid>
      <description>Background The U.S. Department of Education launched College Scorecard in September 2015 as a means of gathering more data on degree-granting institutions, the demographics of college students, and the status of alumni of these institutions [1]. By doing so, the U.S. Department of Education hopes to empower students to make more informed college decisions through a data-driven approach. Considering the soaring cost of higher education as well as the accompanying rise of student debt, prospective students can greatly benefit from such information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Towards reproducible computational drug discovery</title>
      <link>https://hrishikeshh.github.io/finalweb/projects/reproducible-computational-drug-discovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 23:15:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hrishikeshh.github.io/finalweb/projects/reproducible-computational-drug-discovery/</guid>
      <description>Abstract The reproducibility of experiments has been a long standing impediment for further scientific progress. Computational methods have been instrumental in drug discovery efforts owing to its multifaceted utilization for data collection, pre-processing, analysis and inference. This article provides an in-depth coverage on the reproducibility of computational drug discovery. This review explores the following topics: (1) the current state-of-the-art on reproducible research, (2) research documentation (e.g. electronic laboratory notebook, Jupyter notebook, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
